Marcel Breuer
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Project Files, 1921-1986, Series 8:; (Boxes 8-23, 36-40, OVs 43-57; Reels 5720-5737; 27.6 linear feet)
  - Residences, 1923-1982, 8.17:
    This subseries has been divided into 3 sub-subseries of dwellings that have been grouped according to the purpose for which they were built. Each sub-subseries is arranged alphabetically. Sub-subseries are: Miscellaneous House Designs for Single Families; Residences Designed as Commissions; and Multidwelling Apartment Housing Projects.
    - Miscellaneous House Designs for Single Families, 1923-1946, 8.17.1:
      This subseries is arranged alphabetically and consists of 6 project files concerning houses, including prefabricated structures, designed for nonspecific single families.
      - Apartment. Photograph of plans, 1923 (Box 28, Reel 5734, Frame 1245-1246)
      - 1200 Square Foot House, Florida. Floor plan; photographs of drawings, 1944, (oversized material housed in Box 40) (Box 28, Reel 5734, Frame 1248-1253)
      - Oversized 1200 Square Foot House, Florida. Floor plan; photographs of drawings, 1944, (oversized material housed in Box 40) (Box 28, Reel 5734, Frame 1248-1253)
      - Kleinmetallhaus ("small metal house"). Photographs of plans and drawings for a prefabricated house, 1925 (Box 28, Reel 5734, Frame 1255-1259)
      - Plas-2-Point Demountable Houses. Photographs of plans and model, 1942 (Box 28, Reel 5734, Frame 1261-1270)
      - Small House Competition. Photographs of plans, 1946 (Box 28, Reel 5734, Frame 1272-1278)
      - Yankee Portables. Photographs of plans and drawings, 1942 (Box 28, Reel 5734, Frame 1280-1283)
    - Residences Designed as Commissions, 1925-1982, 8.17.2:
      This subseries is arranged alphabetically and consists of 101 project files concerning the construction of residences for specific individuals. When the same individual has commissioned more than one residence, they are listed chronologically.
      - Aspen House, Aspen, Colorado, 1950-1960 (Box 28, Reel 5734)
        - Smith House, Aspen Colorado Contract, (Filmed in wrong order, the Smith House file is filed in Box 31. The remaining Smith House materials are filmed on reel 5734) (Box 28, Reel 5734, Frame 1294-1296)
        - Contract, (Filmed in wrong order, link appears at Reel 5734, 1294-1296) (Box 28, Reel 5734, Frame 1294-1296)
        - Photographs of plans and drawing (Box 28, Reel 5734, Frame 1297-1300)
        - Clippings (Box 28, Reel 5734, Frame 1301-1305)
      - Aufricht House, Addition, Mamaroneck, New York. Contracts, 1951-1953 (Box 28, Reel 5734, Frame 1307-1313)
      - Boroschek Apartment Berlin, Germany. Photographs of completed project, interior, 1930 (Box 28, Reel 5734, Frame 1315-1319)
      - Boyarsky House, Lawrence, New York. Contract, 1979 (Box 28, Reel 5734, Frame 1321-1332)
      - Bratti House, New Canaan, Connecticut. Photograph of plans, 1976 (Box 28, Reel 5734, Frame 1334-1335)
      - Breuer Apartment Berlin, Germany. Photographs of completed project, interior, 1928 (Box 28, Reel 5734, Frame 1337-1340)
      - Breuer House, Lincoln, Massachusetts, 1939 (Box 28, Reel 5734)
        - Photographs of plans, (Oversized material housed in OV 50) (Box 28, Reel 5734, Frame 1342-1343)
        - Photographs of completed project, exterior (Box 28, Reel 5734, Frame 1344-1349)
        - Photographs of completed project, interior (Box 28, Reel 5734, Frame 1350-1357)
        - Negatives (Box 28, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
        - Oversized photographs of plans, (Oversized material scanned with Box 28, Reel 5734, Frames 1342-1343) (Box OV 50, Reel 5734)
      - Breuer House I, New Canaan, Connecticut, 1947 (Box 28, Reel 5734)
        - Photographs of plans and construction, (oversized material housed in Box 40) (Box 28, Reel 5734, Frame 1359-1364)
        - Photographs of completed project, exterior, (2 folders) (Box 28, Reel 5734, Frame 1365-1393)
        - Photographs of completed project, interior (Box 28, Reel 5734, Frame 1394-1406)
        - Negatives (Box 28, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
        - Color transparencies (Box 28, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
        - Clippings (Box 28, Reel 5735, Frame 12-18)
        - Oversized photographs of plans and construction, (oversized material scanned with Box 28, Reel 5734, Frames 1359-1364) (Box 40, Reel 5734)
      - Breuer Cottage, Wellfleet, Massachusetts, 1948 (Box 28, Reel 5735)
        - Photographs of plans and drawings (Box 28, Reel 5735, Frame 20-26)
        - Contact sheet photographs of completed project, exterior and interior (Box 28, Reel 5735, Frame 27-29)
        - Photographs of completed project, exterior (Box 28, Reel 5735, Frame 30-32)
        - Photographs of completed project, interior (Box 28, Reel 5735, Frame 33-37)
        - Negatives and color transparencies (Box 28, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
      - Breuer House II, New Canaan, Connecticut, 1951-1980 (Box 28, Reel 5735)
        - Photographs of plans (Box 28, Reel 5735, Frame 39-41)
        - Photographs of completed project, exterior, (3 folders) (Box 28, Reel 5735, Frame 42-69)
          (includes a photograph by Tamás Breuer)
        - Photographs of completed project, interior (Box 28, Reel 5735, Frame 70-82)
        - Negatives, (2 folders) (Box 28, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
        - Color transparencies (Box 28, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
        - Clippings (Box 28, Reel 5735, Frame 83-110)
      - Caesar House, Lakeville, Connecticut, 1951-1953 (Box 28, Reel 5735)
        - Contract (Box 28, Reel 5735, Frame 112-113)
        - Photographs of plans (Box 28, Reel 5735, Frame 114)
        - Photographs of completed project, exterior, (2 folders) (Box 28, Reel 5735, Frame 115-134)
        - Photographs of completed project, interior (Box 28, Reel 5735, Frame 135-136)
        - Negatives (Box 28, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
        - Color transparencies (Box 28, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
        - Clipping (Box 28, Reel 5735, Frame 137)
      - Calabi House, Lagrangeville, New York. Contract, 1953 (Box 28, Reel 5735, Frame 139-141)
      - Chamberlain Cottage, Wayland, Massachusetts, 1940 (Box 28, Reel 5735)
        - Photographs of plans, (oversized material housed in Box 40) (Box 28, Reel 5735, Frame 143-146)
        - Photographs of completed project, exterior (Box 28, Reel 5735, Frame 147-149)
        - Photographs of completed project, interior (Box 28, Reel 5735, Frame 150-151)
        - Negatives and color transparencies (Box 28, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
        - Clippings (Box 28, Reel 5735, Frame 152-155)
        - Oversized photographs of plans, (oversized material scanned with Box 28, Reel 5735, Frames 143-146) (Box 40, Reel 5735)
      - Clark House, Orange, Connecticut, 1949-1954 (Box 28, Reel 5735)
        - Contract (Box 28, Reel 5735, Frame 157-171)
        - Photographs of plans (Box 28, Reel 5735, Frame 172-174)
        - Photographs of completed project, exterior (Box 28, Reel 5735, Frame 175-185)
        - Photographs of completed project, interior, (2 folders) (Box 28, Reel 5735, Frame 186-194)
        - Negatives and color transparencies (Box 28, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
      - House at Clifton (Crofton Ganes House), Bristol, England. Photographs of completed project, exterior, 1936 (Box 29, Reel 5735, Frame 197-198)
      - Cohen House (location unknown), undated (Box 29, Reel 5735)
        - Photographs of completed project, exterior (Box 29, Reel 5735, Frame 200-202)
        - Photographs of completed project, interior (Box 29, Reel 5735, Frame 203-204)
      - Crall House, Gates Mills, Ohio. Contract, 1953 (Box 29, Reel 5735, Frame 206-207)
      - De Francesco Apartment, Berlin, Germany. Photographs of completed project, interior, 1929 (Box 29, Reel 5735, Frame 209-212)
      - De Gunzburg Houses, Megève, Haute-Savoie, France. Contract, 1964 (Box 29, Reel 5735, Frame 214-217)
      - Englund House, Pleasantville, New York. Contract, 1950 (Box 29, Reel 5735, Frame 219-223)
      - Fischer House and Studio (with Walter Gropius), Newtown, Pennsylvania, 1938 (Box 29, Reel 5735)
        - Photographs of plans (Box 29, Reel 5735, Frame 225-230)
        - Photographs of completed project, exterior, (3 folders) (Box 29, Reel 5735, Frame 231-241)
        - Negatives (Box 29, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
      - Florida House, Miami Heights, Florida. Photographs of plans, drawing, and model, 1945 (Box 29, Reel 5735, Frame 243-251)
      - Ford House, Lincoln, Massachusetts, 1939 (Box 29, Reel 5735)
        - Photograph of plans (Box 29, Reel 5735, Frame 253)
        - Photograph of completed project, exterior (Box 29, Reel 5735, Frame 254-265)
      - Frank House, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1939 (Box 29, Reel 5735)
        - Photographs of plans (Box 29, Reel 5735, Frame 267-269)
        - Contact sheet photographs of completed project, exterior and interior (Box 29, Reel 5735, Frame 270-271)
        - Photographs of completed project, exterior (Box 29, Reel 5735, Frame 272-277)
        - Photographs of completed project, interior, (2 folders); (Oversized material housed in OV 50) (Box 29, Reel 5735, Frame 278-295)
        - Negatives (Box 29, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
        - Oversized photographs of completed project, interior, (Oversized material scanned with Box 29, Reel 5735, Frame 278-295) (Box OV 50, Reel 5735)
      - Gagarin House I, Litchfield, Connecticut, 1953-1966 (Box 29, Reel 5735)
        - Contract (Box 29, Reel 5735, Frame 297-309)
        - Photographs of plans (Box 29, Reel 5735, Frame 310-313)
        - Photographs of completed project, exterior, (2 folders) (Box 29, Reel 5735, Frame 314-348)
        - Photographs of completed project, interior (Box 29, Reel 5735, Frame 349-361)
        - Negatives, (2 folders) (Box 29, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
        - Color transparencies (Box 29, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
        - Clippings (Box 29, Reel 5735, Frame 362-398)
      - Gagarin House II, Litchfield, Connecticut, 1973-1977 (Box 29, Reel 5735)
        - Contract (Box 29, Reel 5735, Frame 400-406)
        - Photographs of plans (Box 29, Reel 5735, Frame 407-408)
        - Photographs of completed project, exterior (Box 29, Reel 5735, Frame 409-412)
        - Photographs of completed project, interior (Box 29, Reel 5735, Frame 413-415)
      - Garces House, Cali, Colombia, 1981-1982 (Box 29, Reel 5735)
        - Photographs of plans, (oversized material housed in Box 40) (Box 29, Reel 5735, Frame 417-422)
        - Photographs of drawings and model, (oversized material housed in Box 40) (Box 29, Reel 5735, Frame 423-432)
        - Oversized photographs of plans, (oversized material scanned with Box 29, Reel 5735, Frames 417-422) (Box 40, Reel 5735)
        - Oversized photographs of drawings and model, (oversized material scanned with Box 29, Reel 5735, Frames 423-432) (Box 40, Reel 5735)
      - Geller House I, Lawrence, Long Island, New York, 1944-1945 (Box 29, Reel 5735)
        - Photographs of plans and model (Box 29, Reel 5735, Frame 434-438)
        - Photographs of completed project, exterior, (2 folders) (Box 29, Reel 5735, Frame 439-451)
        - Photographs of completed project, interior (Box 29, Reel 5735, Frame 452-469)
        - Photographs of chairs designed for house (Box 29, Reel 5735, Frame 470-476)
        - Negatives (Box 29, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
      - Geller House II, Lawrence, Long Island, New York, 1967-1976 (Box 29, Reel 5735)
        - Letters and contracts (Box 29, Reel 5735, Frame 478-574)
        - Photographs of plans and drawings (Box 29, Reel 5735, Frame 575-581)
        - Photographs of completed project, exterior, (4 folders) (Box 29, Reel 5735, Frame 582-613)
          (includes 4 photographs by Tamás Breuer)
        - Photographs of completed project, interior, (4 folders) (Box 29, Reel 5735, Frame 614-637)
        - Negatives, (2 folders) (Box 29, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
        - Color transparency (Box 29, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
        - Clippings (Box 29, Reel 5735, Frame 638-670)
      - Grieco House, Andover, Massachusetts, 1954-1966 (Box 29, Reel 5735)
        - Contract (Box 29, Reel 5735, Frame 672-673)
        - Photographs of plans (Box 29, Reel 5735, Frame 674-675)
        - Photographs of completed project, exterior, (3 folders) (Box 29, Reel 5735, Frame 676-704)
        - Negatives, (2 folders) (Box 29, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
        - Color transparencies (Box 29, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
        - Clippings (Box 29, Reel 5735, Frame 705-738)
      - Gropius House, Dessau, Germany. Photographs of completed project, interior, 1925-1926 (Box 29, Reel 5735, Frame 740-747)
        (includes an aluminum chair and table designed for the house)
      - Gropius House, Lincoln, Massachusetts, 1938 (Box 29, Reel 5735)
        - Photograph of plans (Box 29, Reel 5735, Frame 749)
        - Photographs of completed project, exterior and interior (Box 29, Reel 5735, Frame 750-753)
        - Negatives (Box 29, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
      - Gröte Residence, Dessau, Germany. Photographs of completed project, interior (1926) (Box 29, Reel 5735, Frame 755-758)
      - Haggerty House, Cohasset, Massachusetts, 1938 (Box 29, Reel 5735)
        - Photographs of plans, (Oversized material housed in OV 50) (Box 29, Reel 5735, Frame 760-762)
        - Photographs of model (Box 29, Reel 5735, Frame 763-768)
        - Photographs of construction (Box 29, Reel 5735, Frame 769)
        - Photographs of completed project, exterior, (2 folders) (Box 29, Reel 5735, Frame 770-782)
        - Photographs of completed project, interior (Box 29, Reel 5735, Frame 783)
        - Negatives (Box 29, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
        - Oversized photographs of plans, (Oversized material scanned with Box 29, Reel 5735, Frames 760-762) (Box OV 50, Reel 5735)
      - Halvorson House, Dryberry Lake Area, Kenora, Ontario, Canada, 1958-1960 (Box 29, Reel 5735)
        - Blueprint (Box 29, Reel 5735, Frame 785)
        - Photographs of island site (Box 29, Reel 5735, Frame 786-789)
        - Photographs of construction, (2 folders) (Box 29, Reel 5735, Frame 790-801)
      - Hanson House, Lloyd Harbor, Huntington, Long Island, New York, 1950-1951 (Box 29, Reel 5735)
        - Contract (Box 29, Reel 5735, Frame 803-812)
        - Photographs of plans (Box 29, Reel 5735, Frame 813-814)
        - Photographs of completed project, exterior (Box 29, Reel 5735, Frame 815-819)
        - Photographs of completed project, interior (Box 29, Reel 5735, Frame 820-821)
      - Harnischmacher Apartment Wiesbaden, Germany. Photographs of completed project, interior, 1929 (Box 29, Reel 5735, Frame 823-829)
      - Harnischmacher House I, Wiesbaden, Germany, 1929-1933 (Box 29, Reel 5735)
        - Photographs of plans (Box 30, Reel 5735, Frame 832-835)
        - Photographs of construction (Box 30, Reel 5735, Frame 836-839)
        - Photographs of completed project, exterior, (5 folders) (Box 30, Reel 5735, Frame 840-866)
        - Photographs of completed project, interior, (2 folders) (Box 30, Reel 5735, Frame 867-891)
        - Photographs of chairs designed for house (Box 30, Reel 5735, Frame 892-893)
      - Harnischmacher House II Wiesbaden, Germany. Photographs of completed project, exterior, 1954 (Box 30, Reel 5735, Frame 895-897)
      - Heinersdorff House, Berlin, Germany, 1928-1929 (Box 30, Reel 5735)
        - Photographs of completed project, interior (Box 30, Reel 5735, Frame 899-901)
        - Photographs of multilens window (Box 30, Reel 5735, Frame 902-906)
      - Herrick House, Canajoharie, New York. Contracts, 1949 (Box 30, Reel 5735, Frame 908-916)
      - Heydt Apartment, Berlin, Germany. Photographs of completed project, interior, 1929 (Box 30, Reel 5735, Frame 918-920)
      - Hooper Residence Additions, Baltimore, Maryland, 1949-1950 (Box 30, Reel 5735)
        - Contract (Box 30, Reel 5735, Frame 922-924)
        - Photograph of plans (Box 30, Reel 5735, Frame 925-926)
        - Contact sheet photographs of completed project, exterior and interior (Box 30, Reel 5735, Frame 927-932)
        - Photographs of completed project, exterior (Box 30, Reel 5735, Frame 933-936)
        - Photographs of completed project, interior (Box 30, Reel 5735, Frame 937)
        - Negatives (Box 30, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
        - Color transparencies (Box 30, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
      - Hooper House, Baltimore, Maryland, 1956-1963 (Box 30, Reel 5735)
        - Contract (Box 30, Reel 5735, Frame 939-940)
        - Photographs of completed project, exterior (Box 30, Reel 5735, Frame 941-953)
        - Photographs of completed project, interior (Box 30, Reel 5735, Frame 954-958)
        - Negatives (Box 30, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
        - Clippings (Box 30, Reel 5735, Frame 959-977)
      - Kacmarcik House, St. Paul, Minnesota. Photographs of construction, 1962 (Box 30, Reel 5735, Frame 979-982)
      - Karsten House, Owings Mills, Maryland, 1954-1955 (Box 30, Reel 5735)
        - Contract (Box 30, Reel 5735, Frame 984-991)
        - Photograph of completed project, exterior (Box 30, Reel 5735, Frame 992-993)
      - Kniffin House, New Canaan, Connecticut, 1948 (Box 30, Reel 5735)
        - Photographs of plans (Box 30, Reel 5735, Frame 995-998)
        - Photographs of completed project, exterior, (2 folders) (Box 30, Reel 5735, Frame 999-1010)
        - Photographs of completed project, interior, (3 folders) (Box 30, Reel 5735, Frame 1011-1022)
        - Negatives (Box 30, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
        - Color transparencies (Box 30, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
      - Koerfer House, Moscia, Tessin, Switzerland, 1963-1981 (Box 30, Reel 5735)
        - Letter and contract (Box 30, Reel 5735, Frame 1024-1028)
        - Photographs of plans and drawing (Box 30, Reel 5735, Frame 1029-1038)
        - Photographs of model (Box 30, Reel 5735, Frame 1039-1042)
        - Contact sheet photographs of completed project, exterior and interior (Box 30, Reel 5735, Frame 1043-1065)
        - Photographs of completed project, exterior, (11 folders; oversized material housed in Box 40) (Box 30, Reel 5735, Frame 1066-1171)
        - Photographs of completed project, interior, (5 folders) (Box 30, Reel 5735, Frame 1172-1205)
        - Negatives (Box 30, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
        - Color transparencies (Box 30, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
        - Clippings (Box 30, Reel 5735, Frame 1206-1260)
        - Oversized photographs of completed project, exterior, (oversized material scanned with Box 30, Reel 5735, Frames 1066-1171) (Box 40, Reel 5735)
      - Kreizel House Addition (location unknown). Photographs of plans, 1967 (Box 30, Reel 5735, Frame 1262-1263)
      - Krieger House, Bethesda, Maryland, 1956-1959 (Box 30, Reel 5735)
        - Contract (Box 30, Reel 5735, Frame 1265-1312)
        - Photographs of plans (Box 30, Reel 5735, Frame 1313-1314)
        - Photographs of completed project, exterior (Box 30, Reel 5735, Frame 1315-1318)
        - Photographs of completed project, interior (Box 30, Reel 5735, Frame 1319-1322)
        - Negatives (Box 30, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
      - Laaff House, Andover, Massachusetts, 1955-1961 (Box 30, Reel 5735)
        - Letter and contracts (Box 30, Reel 5735, Frame 1324-1334)
        - Photograph of plans. (Box 30, Reel 5735, Frame 1335-1336)
        - Blueprint (Box 30, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
        - Photographs of completed project, exterior, (3 folders) (Box 30, Reel 5735, Frame 1337-1360)
        - Photographs of completed project, interior (Box 30, Reel 5735, Frame 1361-1364)
        - Negatives (Box 30, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
        - Color transparencies (Box 30, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
        - Clippings (Box 30, Reel 5735, Frame 1365-1385)
        - Clippings (Box 30, Reel 5736, Frame 12-28)
      - Lauck House, Princeton, New Jersey. Letter and contract, 1950 (Box 30, Reel 5736, Frame 30-42)
      - Levy House, Princeton, New Jersey, 1952-1956 (Box 30, Reel 5736)
        - Contract (Box 30, Reel 5736, Frame 44-75)
        - Photographs of plans (Box 30, Reel 5736, Frame 76-77)
        - Photographs of completed project, exterior (Box 30, Reel 5736, Frame 78-83)
        - Photographs of completed project, interior (Box 30, Reel 5736, Frame 84-90)
        - Negatives (Box 30, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
        - Color transparencies (Box 30, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
      - Lewin House, Berlin, Germany. Photographs of completed project, interior, 1929-1930 (Box 30, Reel 5736, Frame 92-96)
      - Margolius House, Palm Springs, California. Photographs of plans, 1938-1939 (Box 31, Reel 5736, Frame 99-102)
      - Marshad House, Croton-on-Hudson, New York. Contracts, 1949-1950 (Box 31, Reel 5736, Frame 104-112)
      - Martine House, Stamford, Connecticut. Photographs of model, 1946 (Box 31, Reel 5736, Frame 114)
      - McComb House, Poughkeepsie, New York. Contract, 1950 (Box 31, Reel 5736, Frame 116-120)
      - McGinnis Apartment, Biltmore, New York, New York. Blueprint, 1955 (Box 31, Reel 5736, Frame 122-124)
      - McGinnis House, Charlmont, Massachusetts, 1955-1956 (Box 31, Reel 5736)
        - Notes and memoranda (Box 31, Reel 5736, Frame 126-136)
        - Photographs of site and exterior of wooden lodge with chimney dated 1902, and interior of lodge (Box 31, Reel 5736, Frame 137-142)
      - McMullen Beach House, Mantoloking, New Jersey, 1960-1964 (Box 31, Reel 5736)
        - Photographs of plans (Box 31, Reel 5736, Frame 144-145)
        - Photographs of completed project, exterior (Box 31, Reel 5736, Frame 146-154)
        - Photographs of completed project, interior (Box 31, Reel 5736, Frame 155-158)
        - Negatives (Box 31, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
        - Color transparencies (Box 31, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
        - Clippings (Box 31, Reel 5736, Frame 159-186)
      - Melder House, Mährisch-Ostrau, Czechoslovakia. Photographs of drawing and model, 1928-1930 (Box 31, Reel 5736, Frame 188-193)
      - Mills House, New Canaan, Connecticut, 1950 (Box 31, Reel 5736)
        - Photograph of construction (Box 31, Reel 5736, Frame 194)
        - Photographs of completed project, exterior (Box 31, Reel 5736, Frame 195)
      - Moholy-Nagy Apartment and Studio, Berlin, Germany. Photograph of completed project, interior, 1926 (Box 31, Reel 5736, Frame 197-198)
      - Muche House, Dessau, Germany. Photograph of desk, 1926 (Box 31, Reel 5736, Frame 200)
      - Neumann House, Croton-on-Hudson, New York, 1953-1972 (Box 31, Reel 5736)
        - Contracts (Box 31, Reel 5736, Frame 202-232)
        - Blueprint for indoor pool; photographs of plans (Box 31, Reel 5736, Frame 233-237)
        - Photographs of completed project, exterior, (4 folders) (Box 31, Reel 5736, Frame 238-263)
        - Photographs of completed project, interior (Box 31, Reel 5736, Frame 264-269)
        - Negatives, (2 folders) (Box 31, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
        - Color transparencies (Box 31, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
        - Clippings (Box 31, Reel 5736, Frame 270-283)
      - Northman Apartment, Berlin, Germany. Photograph of completed project, interior undated (Box 31, Reel 5736, Frame 285-286)
      - Pack House, Scarsdale, New York, 1950-1951 (Box 31, Reel 5736)
        - Contract (Box 31, Reel 5736, Frame 288-300)
        - Photographs of plans (Box 31, Reel 5736, Frame 301-303)
        - Photographs of completed project, exterior (Box 31, Reel 5736, Frame 304-311)
        - Photographs of completed project, interior (Box 31, Reel 5736, Frame 312-318)
        - Negatives (Box 31, Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
      - Picker House, Lake Carmel, New York. Contracts, 1972-1973 (Box 31, Reel 5736, Frame 320-352)